popQuizData = [
    {
    question: 'What does the acronym A.D.H.D. stand for?',
    answers: ['Addictive Diabulimia Hyperphagial Diabetes', 'Adult Dialectic Hysteriacal Doubiety', 'Attention Defecit Hyperactivity Disorder', 'Autistic Developmental Hyperexcitable Displacement'],
    correctAnswer: 'Attention Defecit Hyperactivity Disorder',
    view: 'multiple-choice', 
    },
    {
    question: 'Medication is only one of the many methods, of treating the symptoms of A.D.H.D.. What other holistic methods, when paired with medication, have shown great success in treating A.D.H.D.?',
    answers: ['Routine Exercise', 'Support', 'Nutrition', 'Personalized Natural Supplements'],
    correctAnswer: ['Routine Exercise', 'Support', 'Nutrition', 'Personalized Natural Supplements'],
    view: 'multiple-answer',
    },
    {
    qquestion: '30 - 65% of children diagnosed with A.D.H.D. will have disabling symptomsinto adulthood?',
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
    view: 'boolean',
    },
    {
    question: 'Hundreds of studies conclude that the ________ , _______  and _______ shut down, when the patients tried to concentrate, focus or follow-through with a task',
    answers: ['Grey Matter', 'Cerebellum', 'Hippocampus', 'Prefrontal Cortex'],
    correctAnswer: ['Cerebellum', 'Prefrontal Cortex'],
    view: 'multiple-answer',
    },
    {
    question: 'A.D.H.D. has been found in every country it has been studied. It is not caused by bad parenting or teaching.',
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
    view: 'boolean',
    },
    {
    question: 'The national average of people who drop out of high school is _____ ! With that in mind, _____ of people with A.D.H.D. never finish High School.',
    answers: ['9%, 32%', '10%, 3%', '8%, 70%', '7%, 45%'],
    correctAnswer: '9%, 32%',
    view: 'multiple-choice',
    },
    {
    question: 'A.D.D. is now called "inattentive" A.D.H.D.',
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true',
    view: 'boolean',
    },
    {
    question: 'A.D.H.D. is more common in ______ .',
    answers: ['Women', 'Men'],
    correctAnswer: 'Women',
    view: 'multiple-choice',
    },
    {
    question: 'Inattentive A.D.H.D. is associated with ______  along with a tremendous sense of under acchievement and lonliness.',
    answers: ['Alzheimers', 'Drug Abuse', 'Obesity', 'Type 2 Diabetes', 'Job Failures'],
    correctAnswer: ['Alzheimers', 'Drug Abuse', 'Obesity', 'Type 2 Diabetes', 'Job Failures'],
    view: 'multiple-answer',
    },
    {
    question: 'ADHD is not the most common learning and behavior problem in children, and  <b> ADULTS!</b>',
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'false',
    view: 'boolean',
    }

];

